<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</title>
    <link>https://teapowered.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 01:35:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://teapowered.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 01:35:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/notes/</guid>
      <description>li { margin-bottom: 1.5em };   Computer Vision and Computational Photography &amp;mdash; this guide provides a (relatively) gentle introduction to concepts and algorithms in both computer vision and computational photography, starting from basic image processing, building up to &amp;ldquo;old school&amp;rdquo; vision techniques like the Hough transform for shape detection and Lucas-Kanade for motion estimation, and closing out with modern machine learning algorithms like principal component analysis and hidden Markov models for facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Pescetarian Recipe Collection</title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 23:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/recipes/</guid>
      <description>A collection of tasty pescetarian recipes that I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered over the years with my personal tweaks and suggestions included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Your Every Move Through Your Devices</title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/posts/mac-address-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/posts/mac-address-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Or, abusing MAC addresses for fun and profit (well, no profit unless you&amp;rsquo;re a massive corporation or the government&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello there,</title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>* { text-align: justify; } I&amp;rsquo;m George.
I study computer science and sometimes cook things. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly interested in cryptography, peer-to-peer technologies, and applications of virtual and augmented reality. I like to write about these topics in various (albeit rare) posts. I also enjoy longboarding, rock climbing, and searching for the perfect nacho dish.
You can also check out my \(\LaTeX\)&amp;rsquo;d notes for some of the graduate courses I&amp;rsquo;ve taken at the Georgia Institute of Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>