<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blurbs on Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</title>
    <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blurbs on Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 21:22:43 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1627151023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 21:22:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1627151023/</guid>
      <description>How do places whose local economy basically exists because of tourism have the gall to charge people extra money to visit there? Occupancy taxes are a joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1627151146/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 19:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1627151146/</guid>
      <description>If every brand of paper towels claims that 6 of their rolls is the same as 9 &amp;ldquo;regular&amp;rdquo; rolls, doesnt every brand then become a regular roll? Which means 6 rolls = 9 rolls = 13.5 rolls = &amp;hellip; ad infinitum.
Use this one weird trick to get infinite paper towels for life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1626471604/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 14:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1626471604/</guid>
      <description>Machine &amp;ldquo;learning&amp;rdquo; is a misnomer: The modern black-box algorithms that show us things they think we want to see start by learning from our behavior but end by manipulating it.
After all, isn&amp;rsquo;t it much more optimal (and ML just cares about optimality) to slowly convince 10 users that they all want to see 1 thing rather than to show them 10 uniquely-relevant things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1626471682/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 18:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1626471682/</guid>
      <description>America is one of the only first-world countries out there that allows pharmaceuticals to advertise to the public directly. And then we wonder why we&amp;rsquo;re over-medicated&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1623443719/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 13:36:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1623443719/</guid>
      <description>Just learned about parallel construction, where the story that law enforcement tells the public is completely fabricated in order to keep the juicy details secret. It&amp;rsquo;s fascinating to think about this in the context of the recent Bitcoin ransomware bust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 14:51:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986302/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you wanted to graffiti someone else&amp;rsquo;s fence without getting caught. The color of the graffiti isn&amp;rsquo;t important; it&amp;rsquo;s about sending a message. That means you can choose any color paint you want. Naturally, everyone in the neighborhood has access to the same colors (so no particular choice would draw suspicion) except for one: it&amp;rsquo;s a special, rare color that you are known for producing. You aren&amp;rsquo;t the only one who has any, but you did invent it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986295/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:40:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986295/</guid>
      <description>If you know why a rule exists, you know when it&amp;rsquo;s okay to break it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607203804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 13:30:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607203804/</guid>
      <description>Just realized that the pending ubiquity of self-driving cars will mean every road-accessible inch of our planet will be under a state of constant surveillance thanks to the dozens of high-resolution cameras that will be on every vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606114044/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 22:47:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606114044/</guid>
      <description>At what point did America&amp;rsquo;s materialistic superiority over the Soviet Union transition into a religion of consumerism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606086434/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 15:07:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606086434/</guid>
      <description>Has anyone ever considered the fact that since Google is often the provider of free WiFi at most Starbucks, it can secretly man-in-the-middle all of the hotspot&amp;rsquo;s traffic since it&amp;rsquo;s also a trusted SSL certificate provider? Of course, this would be relatively easy to catch (for example, by noticing that Bing&amp;rsquo;s cert is verified by Google rather than Microsoft), but the potential is still unnerving&amp;hellip; All it would take is a few targeted, hard-to-spot interceptions to gain backdoors on many, many systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606005885/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 16:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606005885/</guid>
      <description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t it odd how more and more normalized it is to have a chemical buffer between our conscious mind and the real world? From the innocence of sipping on a work-day beer to dependence on caffeine consumption for productivity to the absurdity of same-hour marijuana delivery, it seems our grasp on the world around us slips deeper and deeper into the murky waters of substance-induced thought with each passing day / normalized drug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1605610261/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 02:51:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1605610261/</guid>
      <description>There are only two classes worth thinking about: worker and ruler.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
