<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blurbs on Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</title>
    <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blurbs on Bits, Bytes, Late Nights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 14:51:35 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 14:51:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986302/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you wanted to graffiti someone else&amp;rsquo;s fence without getting caught. The color of the graffiti isn&amp;rsquo;t important; it&amp;rsquo;s about sending a message. That means you can choose any color paint you want. Naturally, everyone in the neighborhood has access to the same colors (so no particular choice would draw suspicion) except for one: it&amp;rsquo;s a special, rare color that you are known for producing. You aren&amp;rsquo;t the only one who has any, but you did invent it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986295/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:40:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607986295/</guid>
      <description>If you know why a rule exists, you know when it&amp;rsquo;s okay to break it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607203804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 13:30:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1607203804/</guid>
      <description>Just realized that the pending ubiquity of self-driving cars will mean every road-accessible inch of our planet will be under a state of constant surveillance thanks to the dozens of high-resolution cameras that will be on every vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606114044/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 22:47:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606114044/</guid>
      <description>At what point did America&amp;rsquo;s materialistic superiority over the Soviet Union transition into a religion of consumerism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606086434/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 15:07:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606086434/</guid>
      <description>Has anyone ever considered the fact that since Google is often the provider of free WiFi at most Starbucks, it can secretly man-in-the-middle all of the hotspot&amp;rsquo;s traffic since it&amp;rsquo;s also a trusted SSL certificate provider? Of course, this would be relatively easy to catch (for example, by noticing that Bing&amp;rsquo;s cert is verified by Google rather than Microsoft), but the potential is still unnerving&amp;hellip; All it would take is a few targeted, hard-to-spot interceptions to gain backdoors on many, many systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606005885/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 16:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1606005885/</guid>
      <description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t it odd how more and more normalized it is to have a chemical buffer between our conscious mind and the real world? From the innocence of sipping on a work-day beer to dependence on caffeine consumption for productivity to the absurdity of same-hour marijuana delivery, it seems our grasp on the world around us slips deeper and deeper into the murky waters of substance-induced thought with each passing day / normalized drug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1605610261/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 02:51:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teapowered.dev/blurbs/blurb-1605610261/</guid>
      <description>There are only two classes worth thinking about: worker and ruler.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
